{"id": 54932, "text": "Virgil, how would you describe this book overall?", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 6, "PERSON"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54933, "text": "Is it like sort of his memoir of his time in the White House or is it like sort of a roadmap for how we can get back there?", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[49, 60, "FACILITY"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54934, "text": "It's both.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54935, "text": "It's both.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54936, "text": "All right.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54937, "text": "Chapter one is \"Started From the Bottom.\"", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[8, 11, "QUANTITY"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54938, "text": "Now we're here!", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54939, "text": "Chapter one, editor's notes, \"Dan, you can't call it, 'Hitta, We Made It. '\"", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[8, 11, "QUANTITY"], [30, 33, "PERSON"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54940, "text": "[laughter]", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54943, "text": "It's the story of how he got involved in politics.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[41, 49, "CONCEPT"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54944, "text": "I'll spare you the details and get to some parts I found funny.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54945, "text": "\"In my junior year at Georgetown University, I met a guy named Chad Griffin.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[22, 43, "ORGANIZATION"], [63, 75, "PERSON"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54946, "text": "He was ahead of, he was a year ahead of me in school, but a few years older.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54947, "text": "He was moving into the famously pink row house.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54948, "text": "We rented on prospect street right off campus, (you know, that famous pink house.)", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54949, "text": "We needed a seventh guy to move into our group house so we could afford the rent and he needed a place to live.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54950, "text": "Chad was from Rural Arkansas and had been a student at Ouachita Baptist University in Arkansas.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [20, 28, "LOCATION"], [55, 82, "PERSON"], [86, 94, "LOCATION"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54951, "text": "When Bill Clinton decided to run, Chad interned for Deedee Myers, who was press secretary in that campaign and eventually the White House.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[5, 17, "PERSON"], [34, 38, "PERSON"], [52, 64, "PERSON"], [126, 137, "GPE"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54952, "text": "Chad was good at his job and got offered a full time position on the campaign.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54953, "text": "When Clinton won, he went to the White House as a staffer at age 19.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[5, 12, "PERSON"], [33, 44, "GPE"], [65, 67, "QUANTITY"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54954, "text": "Among other things, he got to see the world, helping shepherd the media around during Bill Clinton's travels.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[86, 100, "PERSON"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54955, "text": "\"After a couple of years in the White House, Chad came to Georgetown to finish his college degree.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[45, 49, "PERSON"], [32, 43, "GPE"], [58, 68, "LOCATION"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54956, "text": "Chad had great stories about working on the Clinton campaign and the White House and it occurred to me maybe working on a presidential campaign, and maybe working in the White House could be a good way station on the path to law school.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [44, 51, "PERSON"], [69, 80, "GPE"], [170, 181, "GPE"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54957, "text": "Certainly better than being a paralegal at some law firm.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54958, "text": "while taking practice LSATS on my lunch break.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54959, "text": "Not to mention since my Dukakis debate, politics had become one of the subjects I followed with trivial pursuit-like intensity.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[24, 31, "PERSON"], [40, 48, "CONCEPT"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54960, "text": "Old plan: Go to law school, become a lawyer, probably hate my life.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54961, "text": "New Plan, go work on a presidential campaign, work in the White House, go to law school, become a lawyer, hate my life, but have done and seen some cool things first.\"", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[58, 69, "GPE"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54962, "text": "So remember: it's cool.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54963, "text": "Yeah, Chad, actually the reason he needed to live with all these 12 year olds who were one of the 85 million comms directors for Barack Obama, such an older man, was he got kicked out of his other house for getting too much pussy.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[6, 10, "PERSON"], [129, 141, "PERSON"], [98, 108, "QUANTITY"], [65, 67, "QUANTITY"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54964, "text": "That's too cool.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54965, "text": "I've got to say I'm very disappointed in this origin story.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54966, "text": "I assume that the Lady of the Wonk rose out of the Potomac river and handed him the Enchanted Lanyard, this was much more boring.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[51, 64, "LOCATION"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54967, "text": "When Chad moved into their Alpha house, was Dan Phif-Dawg a virgin?", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[5, 9, "PERSON"], [44, 47, "PERSON"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54968, "text": "At that point, he ends up interning for the White House and it turns out one day he said - the Bill Clinton White House, and one day he's actually very useful.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[44, 55, "GPE"], [95, 107, "PERSON"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54969, "text": "His unique set of skills come in handy.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54970, "text": "[blowjob noises][laughter]", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54971, "text": "No, uh, somebody needed set of fingerprints on a gun [laughter] to toss next to Vince Foster's body.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[80, 94, "PERSON"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54972, "text": "\"Gore was being investigated by several congressional committees, the FBI and every investigative reporter on the planet.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[1, 5, "PERSON"], [70, 73, "GPE"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54973, "text": "This was the, uh, the 1996 campaign finance-\"", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[22, 26, "TIME"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54974, "text": "Oh Man.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54975, "text": "The Chinese, the Chinese phone calls!", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[4, 11, "NORP"], [17, 24, "NORP"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54976, "text": "\"Every reporter and Republican wanted to muddy up the likely Democratic nominee.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[20, 30, "NORP"], [61, 79, "NORP"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54977, "text": "Everyday the office, we get a request for some set of documents even with tracking numbers.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54978, "text": "Finding the requested memo or email was very time intensive.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54979, "text": "Early in my tenure, one of the attorneys in the counsel's office came in and asked for a very specific memo about a very specific event that was under scrutiny.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54980, "text": "'I need this by the end of the day,' he said, and turned to go.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54981, "text": "\"Wait, this will just take a minute,' I said, walked over the shelf, grabbed the binder and opened it to a certain page.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54982, "text": "'Is this the one you're looking for?'", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54983, "text": "He looked at me like I had a third arm growing out of my head.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[29, 34, "ORDINAL"]], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54984, "text": "'How did you know where that was?'", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54985, "text": "'I have copied and filed these things so many times that I remember the numbers.\"", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54986, "text": "Word got around to the lawyers, researchers, and communication staff who needed quick access to the documents that I was the intern to ask.", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
{"id": 54987, "text": "In hindsight, I was treated a little like Rain Man for this parlor trick, but at the time I loved it.\"", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": "admin", "labels": [], "ep_id": "chapo"}
